Today I'm going to take you back into time and I'm going to show you one of my grandmother's favorite things to make the kids and that was sweet bruschetta.
Sweet bruschetta is just the mixing of different things chopped up and baked in the oven.
But today we're going to show you one for the kids and especially the big kids like me.
I mean this is nice.
You're going to use a whole bunch of things like bananas is the main thing.
When you put in beneath that flame, it glazes and just comes out spectacular.
I'm going to show you all the ingredients of this recipe.
This is at least 60, 70s years old I think.
This recipe what my grandmother use to do this and I hope you enjoy it, I hope you make it, it's really fun and fast.
The kids will love you for it.
I'll show you the ingredients, utensils it's literally 15 minutes and it's done.
I hope you make it.